# HABIB SEIFZADEH

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER with more than 15 years of hands-on experience in full SDLC of enterprise applications. Expert in object-oriented principles such as SOLID and design patterns as well as architectural styles like MVC. I also have an eye for details, good communication skills, and enthusiasm for facing new challenges.



#### CONTACT

habibseifzadeh@gmail.com

+61 413 024 423

Moncrieff, Canberra, ACT, Australia

@habibseifzadeh

in Habib Seifzadeh

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Programming**

**PHP** Java JavaScript **Python** 

HTML/SCSS

#### **Databases**

MySQL Microsoft SQL **SQLite** 

Frameworks and Methods

Laravel Microsoft MVC VueJS/Vuex

Scrum **Cloud based Platforms** 

**Amazon AWS Issue Tracking** 

(e.g., Azure Devops, Jira, Trello, ...)

**Operating Systems** 

Linux Windows



0000

000

IDEs (especially PhpStorm) **PHPUnit XDebug** Docker **Jenkins** Git

Languages

**English** (Certified NAATI interpreter) Persian

#### **CERTIFICATES**

- LinkedIn top 5% of PHP programmers
- LinkedIn top 15% of object-orientation

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am Habib, a developer and software engineer who not only have extensive experience in IT industry, but also always keen to update my knowledge by using state-of-the-art technologies in the projects. I am able to deliver a wide range of products based on customers' needs, from fast-delivered Wordpress websites to high-quality ones using sophisticated frameworks and tools.

## **WORK HISTORY**

April 2016 - Present

**♀** IPCO Limited, Isfahan

Senior Software Engineer

Some developed websites: http://talayemahdi.ir, http://salamatdorin.ir, http://amanatsoft.ir

September 2005 - March 2016

Dade Varze Mabna Engineering Co.

Developer & Software Engineer

Isfahan

Some developed websites: http://dibabuilding.com.au, http://amanatit.com

#### EDUCATION

September 2003 - July 2006

**♀** Najafabad, Isfahan

Master of Software Enginnering

September 1999 - June 2003 **♀** Najafabad, Isfahan

**Bachelor of Software Enginnering** 

# **ACHIEVEMENTS, HONOURS AND AWARDS**

- ₱ Developed a generic e-shop system, easily adaptable to new businesses. with minimun code change (Have been sold to 5 different businesses)
- ₱ Developed REST APIs to make a VB6 legacy system to be useful again.
- Successfully completed projects from Canada, Iceland and Australia
- Successfully led a team of researchers on a project for Isfahan Municipality (migrating their systems to open-source and realising major cost savings)
- ▼ Improved customer satisfaction by performance tuning of several systems
- ₱ Established continuous integration tools to reduce the deployment costs

#### **GENERAL SKILLS**

**Punctual** Fan of new challenges Believe in synergy Swift learner Critical thinker Meticulous Tolerant **Good Communication Skills** 

### A DAY OVERVIEW

